No one from Koichi's family
knows where he went either.
They're talking about calling the police.
So he really is missing.
Yukako's nowhere to be seen, either…
I feel like it's my fault.
You don't think he's dead, do you?
No, I don't think things
have come to that, yet.
But she's holding him captive.
We've got to find him fast.
I have a feeling we don't have
much time left,
if we want to find him alive.
Damn thing won't open!
I can't believe this is happening!
Q.
IN WHAT YEAR DID COLUMBUS
DISCOVER THE "NEW WORLD"?
THE CORRECT ANSWER
WILL OPEN THE LOCK.
Wait, it was a movie, wasn't it?
But I never watched it
'cause it looked so long!
I think I'm almost there…
1, 4, 0, 0…
What was it…?
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 9
YUKAKO YAMAGISHI
FALLS IN LOVE, PART 2
I washed your underwear and
pajama bottoms, you know.
What's wrong?
Now how am I supposed
to know if you refuse to speak?
I-I'm a freshman in high school.
This is beyond…
I'm not embarrassed.
I feel like a completely pathetic
human being.
Please, would you just stop it?
You hate me now, don't you?
I disgust you, don't I?
Just let me go home!
What could you possibly like about
someone who just peed his pants?
Oh, Koichi, you poor, pitiful thing.
Yukako must be putting your
heart through so much torment.
Yukako is a bad girl.
Nothing I say has any effect!
I-I think I'm gonna cry…
First I wet myself, and now this…
But Koichi…
The moment you said
you were a pathetic human being,
I saw a sparkle deep in your eyes…
I saw something intoxicating.
Like you have an ace up your sleeve.
That is what I like about you.
That is what makes me
want to learn more about you.
And when you're in love,
what's a little poop or snot, right?
I'm surprised you'd worry.
Washing your pants
filled me with joy.
Look!
I'm making an electric chair.
I'll be sure it's ready for
our dinner-time studies.
I was thinking about
making Italian tonight.
I should stock up on olive oil.
We'll have fun.
H-Help me!
She keeps getting fiercer and fiercer!
I've got to escape fast,
o-or she's seriously going to kill me!
But…
How do I get out of here?
But Koichi's got Reverb, though.
Even if someone's keeping him quiet,
he can still call for help, right?
But Reverb has a range of
about 50 meters.
He might've been
taken somewhere isolated.
That could be anywhere!
Wait!
She said she was going
to buy some olive oil.
But I can't imagine
she'd go grocery shopping now
Maybe a phone order?
Could it be…?
It is! A pay phone!
And 48 meters away! Yes!
Just within range!
Reverb is a sound Stand!
Now I can signal Josuke for help!
I don't have any 10 yen coins!
I was taken here in my pajamas!
Should I dial 110?
But she might kill the police!
I'm just gonna have to
contact Josuke somehow!
You were wondering whether there was
a pay phone nearby, weren't you?
Y-Yukako…
I know exactly what you're thinking.
Since I told you I was
going to buy some olive oil,
you thought a pay phone
must be nearby.
Then you reasoned it didn't matter,
because you had no 10 yen coins.
That's what you thought, right?
I-Is there a pay phone?
Hmph. Feigning ignorance, I see.
I would give up on
the notion of calling someone.
You're not taking one step
outside this house.
And just in case, I'm going to go
destroy the phone's 110 button.
Would you like anything?
N-No, I guess not…
W-What is wrong with her?!
S-So that's it…
I can't communicate with anyone…
BEEP BEEP BEEP
What's this writing?
Why is there sound coming
from my hand?
It's calling someone!
I never dialed any number!
Hello? Higashikata speaking.
I got through!
If the right touch tone signals
are transmitted,
a push-button phone will connect!
Hello, Koichi, is it you?
Hey! It's me, Josuke!
Koichi, where are you?
What is that?
I hear waves crashing…
Koichi, you…
You have a power like me!
Yes! Josuke's gonna come here
for sure now!
With a car, it'll only take him
15 to 20 minutes!
I just gotta hold out until then!
Somehow I'll do it!
The sound of waves…
A pay phone…
The only place Koichi could be…
is right here!
Koichi.
Koichi!
She's coming back!
I-I've no choice but to fight!
Open this door, Koichi.
Wh-Why don't you just
break it down then?
A broken door will
definitely make Josuke suspicious!
You've made Yukako very happy.
I'm so happy you have
powers like I do, Koichi.
Though it irritates me
you kept this a secret.
Still, I'm happy you're like me.
Because when a man and a woman are
going to share their lives together,
nothing's more important than
a relationship built on
love and shared values, right?
We have something no one else has.
We can be the perfect couple!
So please, Koichi…
Open the door, okay?
When I tell you to open
the door, you open the door!
I HATE YOU
I hate you! I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you! I hate you!
- Perfect couple?!
- I hate you! I hate you! I hate you!
Can't you understand
how much I hate all this?!
That noise will bombard you
until you renounce your love for me
and cry for forgiveness!
I HATE YOU
What is this?
Such nonsense is inaudible to me.
Huh?!
Th-This isn't…
at all like what happened
with Tamami.
Her delusions are too strong!
I didn't think it'd be
completely useless on her…
I've finally found the one person
I'm bound to
with the red thread of fate.
Some people never find
their soulmate.
You still don't understand
how lucky we are?
Koichi…
My plan was to turn you into
an outstanding man,
but I've changed my mind.
Until you fall in love with me,
you will remain in this house.
You will love me!
Or else…
I might murder you.
No matter what, I can't let her in here…
I need to land one more attack
with Reverb!
If I really go all out,
I'll unleash a sound louder than before.
Reverb!
Something's wrong with Reverb…
It's not moving!
I-Is it dead?
Did my Stand die of despair?
Reverb is dead!
REVERB
N-No! M-My…
Reverb's become completely lifeless!
A Stand is a manifestation
of the soul.
It was too much pressure.
I pushed it too far!
Reverb…
What?!
Wh-What is that?
That's what you call a "Stand"?
What is that Stand?
Get this cabinet out of my way!
She's gonna kill me!
If she comes through that door
and catches me, she'll kill me!
Open this door, Koichi!
Don't come through that door!
If only that door could
blow her far, faraway…
It's gone! It's just a shell.
Where did you put it?
Huh?
I said, where did you put it?!
Huh?!
Th…
That's…
Wh-What is this? My Reverb
i-is alive!
Did it just emerge a new form
from its old body?
What is this?
The design's changed only a little.
Besides, it shrank.
Changing shape
won't do you any good!
I-It's fast!
Wh-What is
this wind?!
It blew her away!
I have no idea how,
but some kind of wind blew her away!
Wh-What just…
happened to me?
That's Reverb's writing on the door…
FWOOSH
So she touched the graffitied door,
and the writing became real!
FWOOSH
The sensation of "Fwoosh"
actually blew her away.
I wished the door would
blow her away…
I had no idea,
but I was actually controlling it!
This is the new Reverb!
Reverb Act 2!
Koichi…
CROWN
So it's them…
The one place I know that's
by the sea with lots of empty houses
is this vacation spot.
Yeah, but, there's tons of
houses around here.
Who knows which one he's in?
Our answer's a phone booth!
Koichi called us from a public phone.
First, we find the phone booth,
then we search the houses nearby.
Yeah.
Sweet, adorable Koichi belongs to me.
And I'll never let
anyone else have him.
I suggest you keep
your distance, Yukako.
You should take my word for it…
There's no way you can
compete with Reverb Act 2's abilities.
You can't keep me here.
Now my left eyelid is twitching.
Since I was a kid, getting upset
always set off my orbicularis oculi,
like I was about to get violent.
You know, one stupid
little modification
doesn't suddenly make you
a big shot on campus!
I'm going to have to get
a little rough now!
It's hot!
H-How could you?!
You burned my hand!
You flattop-wearing piece of shit!
When you said "get a little rough,"
did you mean show off
your vulgar mouth?
How dare you do this to me?!
Snot-nosed shrimp!
You are mine!
You belong to me,
yet you dare defy me?!
I own you!
Reverb Act 2!
I missed?
Josuke.
I heard it.
It sounded like something broke.
Hey, I think it's that house.
I can't believe she can
make her hair grow this much…
Her soul is too strong.
It's a dark, vindictive soul…
Reverb was it?
Now that the secret's out,
your abilities disappoint me.
All I have to do is keep
from touching that writing.
So I'll ask you one more time…
You do love me, don't you?
Go ahead and try to say
you don't love me.
I'll tear you and this house
apart right now.
And if you die, you'll be mine
for all eternity.
You'll remain forever in
my heart as my personal memory.
Answer me now!
I've told you,
but you just don't get it.
That's why I'm in this whole mess.
For the umpteenth time,
I don't like you!
And that's the last time.
You're dead, Koichi!
DOGON
I've already told you this too.
You won't be able to
keep hold of me for long.
You're touching the very writing
that will blow you away.
That flattop-wearing piece of shit's
writing is all over, me that is!
Her hair turned white!
She's not dead, is she?
She's alive!
She might be a deranged she-devil,
but I guess I should
be happy about this.
I wasn't able to keep hold of you,
but I figured out that destroying
your Stand is just as good!
Disrespectful punk!
Idiot!
She can still attack?
Her will is insane!
Shut up!
How dare you,
you pantie-wetting prick?!
How dare you do this to me?!
You made my treasured hair
turn white,
you pathetic little jerk off!
I loved you!
But you will not get away
with doing this to my gorgeous hair!
No one gets away with
undermining my beauty!
I'm gonna yank off your piss-soaked prick
and rip out your insides!
S-Stop…
Silence!
You're gonna end up
like that, too, aren't you?!
What? What was that sound?
Let go of Reverb and
grab hold of something.
The cliff is going to crumble.
When Reverb was listening
for your heartbeat,
it also heard the earth splitting.
Hah! Don't try to bullshit me
to save your own hide!
I've got to let go
to grab onto something else!
Shit!
I-I don't have… time!
BOING
Like I said, the ground crumbled.
Then again,
nothing I say to you sinks in.
You mean
you had placed it there already?
When I was trying
to rip Reverb apart…
you stuck that writing on
the rock beneath the cliff?
When I was trying to kill Koichi,
he was thinking of saving me!
I-I've lost.
No, I lost the moment I met Koichi.
Hey, Koichi! Are you okay?
You all right, Koichi?!
Josuke! Okuyasu!
Where were you guys?! Jeez!
B-But I love him even more now.
I don't care if he gives me
the cold shoulder.
Just thinking about Koichi
makes me happy!
Hey, look! Is that Yukako?
Her hair's turned completely white!
Wow, you're right.
But the way she's smiling
she looks like she couldn't be happier.
And she's looking over here.
Huh?!
You're right. Now that's creepy.
Let's get outta here!
Save me, Josuke!
Don't look at me!
Well, I'll be.
Didja see that, Masaji?
I'm still sober, Gramps!
MORIOH LANDMARK 2
CAPE BOING
DIRECTIONS: ASK A LOCAL FISHERMAN
FOR "CAPE BOING,"
AND HE WILL RESPOND IN KIND
BY TAKING YOU THERE BY BOAT.
Cape Boing…
After apparently witnessing
a young woman jump to her death
only to bounce off the rocks
with a gentle "Boing!" …
a pair of fishermen
created an urban legend
and a new appellation.
Hirose!
You really gave it your all
this time, didn't you?
That's what happens
when you study.
ENGLISH EXAM ANSWER SHEET
TEST 3 KOICHI HIROSE
I don't…
know how I should feel about this.
EPISODE 10
LET'S GO EAT SOME ITALIAN FOOD